[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "What is your take on what is happening?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "on", "what", "is", "happening", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "It's not easy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "easy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Doesn't there eventually have to be a cutoff point here?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "n't", "there", "eventually", "have", "to", "be", "a", "cutoff", "point", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "You know, just 11 years ago I was prime minister of Israel and together with President Clinton we put a far reaching kind of a proposal on the -- on the table.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "just", "11", "years", "ago", "I", "was", "prime", "minister", "of", "Israel", "and", "together", "with", "President", "Clinton", "we", "put", "a", "far", "reaching", "kind", "of", "a", "proposal", "on", "the", "--", "on", "the", "table", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Do you agree with what Rick Perry said?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "what", "Rick", "Perry", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "I don't understand exactly what he meant, in what context he's --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "understand", "exactly", "what", "he", "meant", ",", "in", "what", "context", "he", "'s", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Perry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Is he a friend of Israel?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "friend", "of", "Israel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "You know, I think, first of all, he's president of America.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "he", "'s", "president", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Is it inflammatory?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "inflammatory", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "I think that I do not pretend to enter into the American political debate.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "I", "do", "not", "pretend", "to", "enter", "into", "the", "American", "political", "debate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", ":", "IN", "POS", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "If he comes out with these kind of statement, isn't that dangerous?", "question_tokens": ["If", "he", "comes", "out", "with", "these", "kind", "of", "statement", ",", "is", "n't", "that", "dangerous", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "That's up to -- that's up to the American people.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "up", "to", "--", "that", "'s", "up", "to", "the", "American", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Prime Minister Netanyahu"]}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "I mean the moment the Palestinians are circumnavigating you to the United Nations, is it not the time, as many people are crying out for, for you and Prime Minister Netanyahu to get together and say, we're going to make this happen, we're going to do a deal, we're going to take more pain in negotiation than we would wish to because the bigger picture is more important?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "the", "moment", "the", "Palestinians", "are", "circumnavigating", "you", "to", "the", "United", "Nations", ",", "is", "it", "not", "the", "time", ",", "as", "many", "people", "are", "crying", "out", "for", ",", "for", "you", "and", "Prime", "Minister", "Netanyahu", "to", "get", "together", "and", "say", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "make", "this", "happen", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "do", "a", "deal", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "take", "more", "pain", "in", "negotiation", "than", "we", "would", "wish", "to", "because", "the", "bigger", "picture", "is", "more", "important", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "I believe Prime Minister Netanyahu genuinely believes in the need to move forward and ready to take the risks to pay the painful price.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "Prime", "Minister", "Netanyahu", "genuinely", "believes", "in", "the", "need", "to", "move", "forward", "and", "ready", "to", "take", "the", "risks", "to", "pay", "the", "painful", "price", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United Nations"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel", "Lebanon"]}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "What is the risk that you're talking about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "risk", "that", "you", "'re", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "It's -- you know, Israel, we -- for example, we pulled out under my order as a prime minister from Lebanon.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "Israel", ",", "we", "--", "for", "example", ",", "we", "pulled", "out", "under", "my", "order", "as", "a", "prime", "minister", "from", "Lebanon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "What is it like to be the Israeli defense minister in the middle of all this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "like", "to", "be", "the", "Israeli", "defense", "minister", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "all", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "It's clear we have to rely upon ourselves, that it's a tough neighborhood.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "clear", "we", "have", "to", "rely", "upon", "ourselves", ",", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "tough", "neighborhood", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "-- with a whole lot of Irans?", "question_tokens": ["--", "with", "a", "whole", "lot", "of", "Irans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "Let me tell you -- I feel the pain for Mubarak.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "tell", "you", "--", "I", "feel", "the", "pain", "for", "Mubarak", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Like I said, do you worry that you may end up with a series of mini-Irans coming out of this Arab Spring where you have the Islamists basically controlling these countries in a way they never have before?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "I", "said", ",", "do", "you", "worry", "that", "you", "may", "end", "up", "with", "a", "series", "of", "mini-Irans", "coming", "out", "of", "this", "Arab", "Spring", "where", "you", "have", "the", "Islamists", "basically", "controlling", "these", "countries", "in", "a", "way", "they", "never", "have", "before", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "First of all, we are worried, but a person cannot choose his parents, and a nation cannot choose its neighbors.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "we", "are", "worried", ",", "but", "a", "person", "can", "not", "choose", "his", "parents", ",", "and", "a", "nation", "can", "not", "choose", "its", "neighbors", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arab Spring"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "This is the time to do this deal, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "the", "time", "to", "do", "this", "deal", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "It was the time 10 years and 20 years.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "the", "time", "10", "years", "and", "20", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VB", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 227, "question": "Do you feel after all these decades you dealt with Palestinian leadership, that the current leadership, even if they don't have complete control over all the elements with the Palestinians, do you feel there is more chance now of doing a deal with the people at the head, Palestinian leadership, than you've had in your lifetime?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "after", "all", "these", "decades", "you", "dealt", "with", "Palestinian", "leadership", ",", "that", "the", "current", "leadership", ",", "even", "if", "they", "do", "n't", "have", "complete", "control", "over", "all", "the", "elements", "with", "the", "Palestinians", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "there", "is", "more", "chance", "now", "of", "doing", "a", "deal", "with", "the", "people", "at", "the", "head", ",", "Palestinian", "leadership", ",", "than", "you", "'ve", "had", "in", "your", "lifetime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "See, only time will tell.", "answer_tokens": ["See", ",", "only", "time", "will", "tell", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "Does your gut instinct tell you that?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "your", "gut", "instinct", "tell", "you", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Still have to be proven.", "answer_tokens": ["Still", "have", "to", "be", "proven", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Yes, yes, it is the biggest moment of my career.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "yes", ",", "it", "is", "the", "biggest", "moment", "of", "my", "career", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "WRB", "IN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "Yes, I mean, someone supremely self-confident like you, how nervous are you?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "someone", "supremely", "self-confident", "like", "you", ",", "how", "nervous", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, if you remember, when you and I first started working together on \"Britain's Got Talent,\" God only knows how that happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "remember", ",", "when", "you", "and", "I", "first", "started", "working", "together", "on", "``", "Britain", "'s", "Got", "Talent", ",", "''", "God", "only", "knows", "how", "that", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "And from what you've edited so far, how confident are you that it's going to be a big hit?", "question_tokens": ["And", "from", "what", "you", "'ve", "edited", "so", "far", ",", "how", "confident", "are", "you", "that", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "a", "big", "hit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, it's like comparing you and I. We're both guys, we're both British, but there's a massive difference between how people respond to you and people respond to me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "like", "comparing", "you", "and", "I.", "We", "'re", "both", "guys", ",", "we", "'re", "both", "British", ",", "but", "there", "'s", "a", "massive", "difference", "between", "how", "people", "respond", "to", "you", "and", "people", "respond", "to", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Is there any truth to the ghastly rumor that you're quite nice in this series or not?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "any", "truth", "to", "the", "ghastly", "rumor", "that", "you", "'re", "quite", "nice", "in", "this", "series", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "Well, at times.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "at", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "From what you've seen now -- you've gone through the auditions -- how good is the talent on U.S. \"X Factor\"?", "question_tokens": ["From", "what", "you", "'ve", "seen", "now", "--", "you", "'ve", "gone", "through", "the", "auditions", "--", "how", "good", "is", "the", "talent", "on", "U.S.", "``", "X", "Factor", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "It's crazily good.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "crazily", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "And how would you deal with it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "would", "you", "deal", "with", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "Well, you don't go into anything contemplating failure, because if you did, you wouldn't make it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "go", "into", "anything", "contemplating", "failure", ",", "because", "if", "you", "did", ",", "you", "would", "n't", "make", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Could you take down \"Idol,\" do you think, in season one?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "take", "down", "``", "Idol", ",", "''", "do", "you", "think", ",", "in", "season", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "``", "NNP", ",", "''", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "NN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "It's impossible to predict.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "impossible", "to", "predict", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Would you like to?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "Did you watch many of the \"Idol\" shows?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "watch", "many", "of", "the", "``", "Idol", "''", "shows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "Did you find it odd, the whole concept of an \"Idol\" without you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "find", "it", "odd", ",", "the", "whole", "concept", "of", "an", "``", "Idol", "''", "without", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Mr. Mean is still there, isn't he, alive and kicking?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Mean", "is", "still", "there", ",", "is", "n't", "he", ",", "alive", "and", "kicking", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "He's there.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mean"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "To those who've lost their jobs in all this, who are really suffering out there, what do you say to them?", "question_tokens": ["To", "those", "who", "'ve", "lost", "their", "jobs", "in", "all", "this", ",", "who", "are", "really", "suffering", "out", "there", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "to", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "WP", "-NONE-", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Well, you know, I had to sort myself out.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "had", "to", "sort", "myself", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "What are you talking about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "talking", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "But you shouldn't an opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "you", "should", "n't", "an", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 428, "question": "Why not?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 429, "answer": "Because we don't live here.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "do", "n't", "live", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "As a leader, how do you think he's doing?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "leader", ",", "how", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "As a leader, I think he's a decent guy, I really do.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "a", "leader", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "a", "decent", "guy", ",", "I", "really", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "You're not on Twitter, are you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "on", "Twitter", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "I can't do it, but I watch it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "do", "it", ",", "but", "I", "watch", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "You're not worried about not getting as many followers as me?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "not", "worried", "about", "not", "getting", "as", "many", "followers", "as", "me", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "You're fanatical about big lights and listened to.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'re", "fanatical", "about", "big", "lights", "and", "listened", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "How impossible has she been to work with?", "question_tokens": ["How", "impossible", "has", "she", "been", "to", "work", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I don't mind you exchanging barbs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "mind", "you", "exchanging", "barbs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "How am I impossible?", "question_tokens": ["How", "am", "I", "impossible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "In a nice way.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "a", "nice", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Have you ever met a bigger ego than Simon?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "met", "a", "bigger", "ego", "than", "Simon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "No, absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Simon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "It must for the nerves alone make things ten times more tense?", "question_tokens": ["It", "must", "for", "the", "nerves", "alone", "make", "things", "ten", "times", "more", "tense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "NNS", "VBN", "NNS", "RBR", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "You know, I started out in a show like this, where I entered the audition, went through the whole process, and went to the city and drove there.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "started", "out", "in", "a", "show", "like", "this", ",", "where", "I", "entered", "the", "audition", ",", "went", "through", "the", "whole", "process", ",", "and", "went", "to", "the", "city", "and", "drove", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "Why are you so awkward watching it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "so", "awkward", "watching", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I don't like watching myself on TV.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "like", "watching", "myself", "on", "TV", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "It's much easier to perform.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "much", "easier", "to", "perform", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Not everybody is like you, Simon, OK?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "everybody", "is", "like", "you", ",", "Simon", ",", "OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "I have heard it all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "heard", "it", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Simon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Paula", "Paula"]}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "Can we talk about Paula Abdul, because obviously, you know, an old -- what does it feel like you, Nicole, to be coming in between the most famous talent show judging desk pairing in history?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "we", "talk", "about", "Paula", "Abdul", ",", "because", "obviously", ",", "you", "know", ",", "an", "old", "--", "what", "does", "it", "feel", "like", "you", ",", "Nicole", ",", "to", "be", "coming", "in", "between", "the", "most", "famous", "talent", "show", "judging", "desk", "pairing", "in", "history", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Growing up, I loved Paula, like I was kind of obsessed with Paula.", "answer_tokens": ["Growing", "up", ",", "I", "loved", "Paula", ",", "like", "I", "was", "kind", "of", "obsessed", "with", "Paula", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paula Abdul", "Nicole"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Everything.", "answer_tokens": ["Everything", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Like what?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "what", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Well, let me show you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "show", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Do your family slightly go, Nicole, what are you up to?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "your", "family", "slightly", "go", ",", "Nicole", ",", "what", "are", "you", "up", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "That's the thing, is like my -- my papa is a priest.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "thing", ",", "is", "like", "my", "--", "my", "papa", "is", "a", "priest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nicole"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Your dad loved that video?", "question_tokens": ["Your", "dad", "loved", "that", "video", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "My grandfather.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "grandfather", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 592, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 593, "answer": "They love it.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "And the crushing answer is no, you're not, are you?", "question_tokens": ["And", "the", "crushing", "answer", "is", "no", ",", "you", "'re", "not", ",", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "I have a boyfriend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "a", "boyfriend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "-- I have ever experienced.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "I", "have", "ever", "experienced", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "When you first met his, was it love at first hand bite?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "first", "met", "his", ",", "was", "it", "love", "at", "first", "hand", "bite", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "I don't -- that would be weird, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "that", "would", "be", "weird", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "You know Louis, right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "Louis", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "Yes, he's a great guy, very cool, brilliant driver, but a cool guy.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "'s", "a", "great", "guy", ",", "very", "cool", ",", "brilliant", "driver", ",", "but", "a", "cool", "guy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Louis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Is that what you need in your life?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "you", "need", "in", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "He is very humble.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "very", "humble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "Does he quite qualify for toy boy status or not?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "quite", "qualify", "for", "toy", "boy", "status", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "No, absolutely not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "absolutely", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "This is not that kind of show, not the kind of show that you do.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "not", "that", "kind", "of", "show", ",", "not", "the", "kind", "of", "show", "that", "you", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Are you excited by this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "excited", "by", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "I'm really excited.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "really", "excited", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110920pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "You got a little crush, don't you ?", "question_tokens": ["You", "got", "a", "little", "crush", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "A little bit, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "little", "bit", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]